<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>Lucas Draney - AI Automation &amp; Business Process Expert</title>
      <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on Lucas Draney - AI Automation &amp; Business Process Expert</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>AI Corporate Psychology</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/capabilities/AI-Corporate-Psychology</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/capabilities/AI-Corporate-Psychology</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[ AI Corporate Psychology The Future of Business Organization The Revolutionary Question: What if you had 100 perfectly untrained employees ready to learn? How would you train and organize them for maximum effectiveness? Now imagine those employees are AI agents - tireless, consistent, and capable of ... ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 19:50:55 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>DevOps Leadership</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/capabilities/DevOps-Leadership</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/capabilities/DevOps-Leadership</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[ DevOps Leadership &amp; Cultural Transformation Expert in Culture, Technical Implementation, and Scalable Operations Professional Identity: DevOps Manager with deep expertise in organizational culture, technical automation, team training, and scalable system implementation. ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 19:50:55 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Tech Stack</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/capabilities/Tech-Stack</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/capabilities/Tech-Stack</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[ Technology Stack &amp; Technical Capabilities Comprehensive Development and Operations Expertise Deep technical expertise across modern development stacks, infrastructure automation, and enterprise integration platforms. ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 19:50:55 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Pure Earth Labs Transformation</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/case-studies/Pure-Earth-Labs-Transformation</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/case-studies/Pure-Earth-Labs-Transformation</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[ Pure Earth Labs Digital Transformation Complete Manufacturing Operations Overhaul &amp; AI Integration Challenge: Transform a growing cosmetics manufacturing company from manual processes to fully integrated, automated operations while maintaining quality standards and accelerating growth. ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 19:50:55 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Repository Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/case-studies/Repository-Portfolio</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/case-studies/Repository-Portfolio</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[ Active Development Portfolio Current Projects &amp; Specialized Expertise Based on active repositories and ongoing development work, showcasing real-world implementations across AI automation, business process optimization, and technical infrastructure. ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 19:50:55 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Consultation Process</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/contact/Consultation-Process</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/contact/Consultation-Process</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[ Consultation Process Strategic Assessment &amp; Custom Proof of Concept Development Ready to transform your manufacturing operations through intelligent automation and DevOps excellence? Let’s discuss your specific challenges and develop a customized solution strategy. ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 19:50:55 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Lucas Draney - AI Automation &amp; Business Process Expert</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[ Transforming business operations through AI agents, Monday.com automation, Inflow inventory management, and custom workflow solutions. Specializing in Claude AI development, OpenAI embeddings, and DevOps automation. ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 19:50:55 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>AI Agent Development</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/services/AI-Agent-Development</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/services/AI-Agent-Development</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[ AI Agent Development Services Custom Intelligent Agents for Business Automation Transform your business operations with purpose-built AI agents that handle complex tasks, provide expert guidance, and integrate seamlessly with your existing systems. ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 19:50:55 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Manufacturing Operations</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/services/Manufacturing-Operations</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/services/Manufacturing-Operations</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[ Manufacturing Operations Optimization Comprehensive Systems Integration for Modern Manufacturing Transform your manufacturing operations through intelligent automation, integrated workflow management, and scalable system architecture. ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 19:50:55 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>